I've decided to run for student body president. If I'm going to become a senator one day, I should get some experience under my belt now.
Andrea Jenkins is also running. She'll give you a run for your money.
Andrea Jenkins is an idiot. I'm by far the better candidate.
Don't be so full of yourself. I'm my vote for Andrea.
Stop kidding around. Let's get down to business. I need your help.
You want me to help you?
Yes. I need you to talk your friends into voting for me.
But you've never given my friends the time of day. All you give them is the cold shoulder.
That's because they've got blue hair and nose rings.
The better than your friends, a bunch of goody-goodies and brown nosers.
That's beside the point. Let's talk about your friends and their votes.
Okay, you scratch my back and I'll scratch yours. If you do my chemistry homework, I'll help you get the votes.
I'm not crazy about that idea. But okay, it's a deal. I hope I can count on you.